[
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called main_camera?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called /camera/image_raw?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called /camera/info?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called /camera/set_exposure?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called /camera/get_info?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node main_camera publish to topic /camera/image_raw?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is node main_camera subscribed to topic /camera/image_raw?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node main_camera publish to topic /camera/info?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is node main_camera subscribed to topic /camera/info?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "To which topics can node main_camera publish?",
    "answer": "/camera/image_raw"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "To which topics is node main_camera subscribed?",
    "answer": "/camera/info"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node main_camera provide service /camera/set_exposure?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "CLIENT",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node main_camera use service /camera/set_exposure as a client?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node main_camera provide service /camera/get_info?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "CLIENT",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node main_camera use service /camera/get_info as a client?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which services does node main_camera provide?",
    "answer": "/camera/set_exposure"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "CLIENT",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which services does node main_camera use as a client?",
    "answer": "/camera/get_info"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE_TYPE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of service /camera/set_exposure?",
    "answer": "my_pkg/srv/SetExposure"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE_TYPE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of service /camera/get_info?",
    "answer": "my_pkg/srv/GetInfo"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TOPIC_TYPE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of topic /camera/image_raw?",
    "answer": "sensor_msgs/msg/Image"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TOPIC_TYPE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of topic /camera/info?",
    "answer": "sensor_msgs/msg/CameraInfo"
  }
]